Welcome to The Voice of Hack The Box.
My name is Sky, and I am your host.
Have you ever heard of Hack The Box?
Have you tried their academy modules?
Have you discovered that reading alone,
however interesting and well-structured the modules may be,
is a little tough to chew on?
Well, boy, do I have some good news for you!
This channel is dedicated to narrating the written content of Hack The Box Academy's modules.
For those of you who don't know,
Hack the Box is a cybersecurity training website
dedicated to a human-first approach to teaching cybersecurity with gamified learning
making the transition from the raw fundamentals to advanced hacking scenarios
as thorough and painless as possible.
One of Hack The Box's many public branches is Hack The Box Academy.
It is a technical, text-book style form of learning with many pages of content
packed full of important information in the bite-sized chunks known as modules.
I should be clear immediately that I am not sponsored by Hack The Box to do this.
I am, at the very least, making a personal learning tool available to the public.
All content I narrate is viewable with a free plan Hack The Box account.
Join me as I take you on a learning adventure deep into Hack The Box Academy's catalogue
with expertly referenced, mercilessly timestamped, and guidingly casual commentary.
Welcome to The Voice of Hack The Box.